Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. (CSEA), American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Local 1000 Records apap015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- CSEA Publications, 1932-2014; 5; 15.04 cubic ft. 2686 Digital Files
  - The Public Sector, 1998 May (Oversized 20, Folder 3)
  - The Public Sector, 1998 June (Oversized 20, Folder 3)
  - The Public Sector, 1998 July (Oversized 20, Folder 3)
  - The Public Sector, 1998 August (Oversized 20, Folder 3)
  - The Public Sector, 1998 September (Oversized 20, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 1998 October (Oversized 21, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 1998 November (Oversized 21, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 1998 December (Oversized 21, Folder 1)
  - CSEA @ Work, 1998-2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The Work Force, 1999 January (Oversized 21, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 1999 February (Oversized 21, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 1999 March (Oversized 21, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 1999 April (Oversized 21, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 1999 May (Oversized 21, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 1999 June (Oversized 21, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 1999 July (Oversized 21, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 1999 August (Oversized 21, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 1999 September (Oversized 21, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 1999 October (Oversized 21, Folder 4)
  - The Work Force, 1999 November (Oversized 21, Folder 4)
  - The Work Force, 1999 December (Oversized 21, Folder 4)
  - Contract Update, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - The Work Force, 2000 January (Oversized 22, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 2000 February (Oversized 22, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 2000 March (Oversized 22, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 2000 April (Oversized 22, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 2000 May (Oversized 22, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 2000 June (Oversized 22, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 2000 July (Oversized 22, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 2000 August (Oversized 22, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 2000 September (Oversized 22, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 2000 October (Oversized 22, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 2000 November (Oversized 22, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 2000 December (Oversized 22, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 2001 January (Oversized 22, Folder 4)
  - The Work Force, 2001 February (Oversized 22, Folder 4)
  - The Work Force, 2001 March (Oversized 22, Folder 4)
  - The Work Force, 2001 April (Oversized 22, Folder 4)
  - The Work Force, 2001 May (Oversized 22, Folder 5)
  - The Work Force, 2001 June (Oversized 22, Folder 5)
  - The Work Force, 2001 July (Oversized 22, Folder 5)
  - The Work Force, 2001 August (Oversized 22, Folder 5)
  - The Work Force, 2001 September (Oversized 22, Folder 6)
  - The Work Force, 2001 October (Oversized 22, Folder 6)
  - The Work Force, 2001 November (Oversized 22, Folder 6)
  - The Work Force, 2001 December (Oversized 22, Folder 6)
  - CSEA Nassau News, 2001-2002 (Oversized 6, Folder 3)
  - Regional Reporter, 2001-2002 (Oversized 6, Folder 4)
  - The Canary, 2001-2005; 2011; 2013-2014 (Oversized 22, Folder 7)
  - The Work Force, 2002 January (Oversized 23, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 2002 February (Oversized 23, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 2002 March (Oversized 23, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 2002 April (Oversized 23, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 2002 May (Oversized 23, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 2002 June (Oversized 23, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 2002 July (Oversized 23, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 2002 August (Oversized 23, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 2002 September (Oversized 23, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 2002 October (Oversized 23, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 2002 November (Oversized 23, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 2002 December (Oversized 23, Folder 3)
  - Advocate, 2002-2009 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The Work Force, 2003 January (Oversized 23, Folder 4)
  - The Work Force, 2003 February (Oversized 23, Folder 4)
  - The Work Force, 2003 March (Oversized 23, Folder 4)
  - The Work Force, 2003 April (Oversized 23, Folder 4)
  - The Work Force, 2003 May (Oversized 23, Folder 5)
  - The Work Force, 2003 June (Oversized 23, Folder 5)
  - The Work Force, 2003 July (Oversized 23, Folder 5)
  - The Work Force, 2003 August (Oversized 23, Folder 5)
  - The Work Force, 2003 September (Oversized 23, Folder 6)
  - The Work Force, 2003 October (Oversized 23, Folder 6)
  - The Work Force, 2003 November (Oversized 23, Folder 6)
  - The Work Force, 2003 December (Oversized 23, Folder 6)
  - CSEA Nassau News, 2003-2004 (Oversized 6, Folder 5)
  - Regional Reporter, 2003-2004 (Oversized 6, Folder 6)
  - The Work Force, 2004 January (Oversized 24, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 2004 February (Oversized 24, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 2004 March (Oversized 24, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 2004 April (Oversized 24, Folder 1)
  - The Work Force, 2004 May (Oversized 24, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 2004 June (Oversized 24, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 2004 July (Oversized 24, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 2004 August (Oversized 24, Folder 2)
  - The Work Force, 2004 September (Oversized 24, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 2004 October (Oversized 24, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 2004 November (Oversized 24, Folder 3)
  - The Work Force, 2004 December (Oversized 24, Folder 3)
  - Labor History Newsletter, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Work Force, 2005 January (Oversized 24, Folder 4)
  - The Work Force, 2005 February (Oversized 24, Folder 4)
  - The Work Force, 2005 March (Oversized 24, Folder 4)
  - The Work Force, 2005 April (Oversized 24, Folder 4)
  - The Work Force, 2005 May (Oversized 24, Folder 5)
  - The Work Force, 2005 June (Oversized 24, Folder 5)
  - The Work Force, 2005 July (Oversized 24, Folder 5)
  - The Work Force, 2005 August (Oversized 24, Folder 5)
  - The Work Force, 2005 September (Oversized 24, Folder 6)
  - The Work Force, 2005 October (Oversized 24, Folder 6)
  - The Work Force, 2005 November (Oversized 24, Folder 6)
  - The Work Force, 2005 December (Oversized 24, Folder 6)
  - Public Employee, 2005 (Box 4)
  - The Work Force, 2006 January (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2006 February (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2006 March (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2006 April (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2006 May (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2006 June (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2006 July (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2006 August (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2006 September (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2006 October (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2006 November (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2006 December (Oversized 25)
  - Retiree News, 2006-2014 (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2007 January (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2007 February (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2007 March (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2007 April (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2007 May (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2007 June (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2007 July-2007 August (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2007 September (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2007 October (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2007 November (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2007 December (Oversized 25)
  - The Work Force, 2008 January (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2008 February (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2008 March (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2008 April (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2008 May (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2008 June (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2008 July-2008 August (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2008 September (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2008 October (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2008 November (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2008 December (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2009 January (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2009 February (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2009 March (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2009 April (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2009 May (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2009 June (Oversized 26)
  - The Work Force, 2009 July-2009 August (Oversized 26)
    - Donna Mead, a Civil Service Employees Association..., 2009 July 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2009 July 1
    - Probation Officers and Civil Service Employees..., 2009 July 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) state..., 2009 July 1
    - Marcia Gould, a Civil Service Employees..., 2009 July 1
    - Warren County workers and Civil Service Employees..., 2009 July 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2009 July 1
    - Capital District DDSO Local President Joseph..., 2009 July 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) was a..., 2009 July 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Western..., 2009 July 1
    - From left, Bess Watts and Pat Martinez, Civil..., 2009 July 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2009 July 1
    - Suffolk County Local President Bill Walsh..., 2009 July 1
    - Southold Unit member Ev Corwin, left, and unit..., 2009 July 1
    - Mental Health Therapy Aide Sandra Martine tells..., 2009 July 1
    - From left, Civil Service Employees Association..., 2009 July 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 July 1
    - Officer Aaron Dean of the Newark Police Department..., 2009 July 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 July 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2009 July 1
    - Bronx Children's Psychiatric Center Local activist..., 2009 July 1
    - Kingsboro Psychiatric Center Local Vice President..., 2009 July 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2009 July 1
    - ?Sally MacDougal, right, of Steuben County, and..., 2009 July 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 July 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2009 July 1
    - Angelo Costanzo shows a Civil Service Employees..., 2009 July 1
    - Brookhaven Supervisor Mark Lesko, right,..., 2009 July 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2009 July 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2009 July 1
    - An illustration by graphic artist Ralph Distin..., 2009 July 1
  - The Work Force, 2009 September (Oversized 26)
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Western..., 2009 September 1
    - VOICE/Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 September 1
    - Southold Unit members listen to unit and local..., 2009 September 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association..., 2009 September 1
    - City of Saratoga Springs Civil Service Employees..., 2009 September 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 September 1
    - Ruby Mims, Erie County Local member, was a PEOPLE..., 2009 September 1
    - Long Island Region members, including Long Island..., 2009 September 1
    - Joseph Lochner, known as "Mr. CSEA," was Civil..., 2009 September 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 September 1
    - State Department of Transportation Syracuse Local..., 2009 September 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Orange..., 2009 September 1
    - Suffolk County Local President Bill Walsh provides..., 2009 September 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Orange..., 2009 September 1
    - Illustration by graphic artist Ralph Distin..., 2009 September 1
    - Rosalind Conti, a Chautauqua County Local..., 2009 September 1
  - The Work Force, 2009 October (Oversized 26)
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)/VOICE..., 2009 October 1
    - Bronx Psychiatric Center Local President Abraham..., 2009 October 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Putnam..., 2009 October 1
    - From left, Civil Service Employees Association..., 2009 October 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2009 October 1
    - Bill Quinn of the Silver Creek Department of..., 2009 October 1
    - The water line remains visible inside the Silver..., 2009 October 1
    - Stephen Delair, Sunmount Developmental Center..., 2009 October 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 October 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association CSEA members,..., 2009 October 1
    - Western Region President Flo Tripi speaks on the..., 2009 October 1
    - Buffalo Mayor Byron Brown addresses the Civil..., 2009 October 1
    - Kim Kopp, Sunmount Development Center Local, was a..., 2009 October 1
    - State Office of Children and Family Services Local..., 2009 October 1
    - Judy Richards, Pat Gooden and Lee Pound, shown at..., 2009 October 1
    - Albany County Unit members and their supporters..., 2009 October 1
    - A powerful flood knocked a hole in a brick wall in..., 2009 October 1
    - Members from Civil Service Employees Association..., 2009 October 1
    - Rachel Baldwin, Buffalo State Employees Local,..., 2009 October 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2009 October 1
    - Southern Region President Billy Riccaldo, Long..., 2009 October 1
    - From left, Civil Service Employees Association..., 2009 October 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) State..., 2009 October 1
    - Damaris Samolinski, far right, a VOICE/Civil..., 2009 October 2
    - Leslie Walls, James E. Christian Memorial Health..., 2009 October 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 October 1
    - In Erie County, hundreds of Civil Service..., 2009 October 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2009 October 1
    - New York State Senator Catherine Young speaks to..., 2009 October 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 October 1
    - Nearly 1,000 Civil Service Employees Association..., 2009 October 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 October 1
    - Lifespire Local President Pam Marshall, flanked by..., 2009 October 1
    - Long Island Region members, including Region..., 2009 October 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2009 October 1
    - Dewayne Parsons, Capital District Psychiatric..., 2009 October 1
    - Cover of the October, 2009, Work Force. In Erie..., 2009 October 1
  - The Work Force, 2009 November (Oversized 26)
    - Cover of the November, 2009, Work Force, 2009 November 1
    - More than 1,000 Civil Service Employees..., 2009 November 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 November 1
    - Nassau County Local 2nd Vice President Lynne..., 2009 November 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Buffalo..., 2009 November 1
    - An illustration by Graphic Artist Ralph Distin,..., 2009 November 1
    - An Onondaga County Local member demonstrating with..., 2009 November 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) workers..., 2009 November 1
    - Santos Guzman, a Civil Service Employees..., 2009 November 1
    - Among those addressing a VOICE and CCPT-NY..., 2009 November 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 November 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2009 November 1
    - Ken Allen, executive director of AFSCME Oregon..., 2009 November 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 November 1
    - VOICE and CCPT-NY activists listen to speakers at..., 2009 November 1
    - Among those addressing a VOICE and CCPT-NY..., 2009 November 1
    - Saratoga Springs Department of Public Works Unit..., 2009 November 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2009 November 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 November 1
    - A traveling display presenting Civil Service..., 2009 November 1
    - Karen Bright of the Madison County Local in the..., 2009 November 1
    - Sullivan County Sheriff's Office Unit Vice..., 2009 November 1
    - Western Region President Flo Tripi examines the..., 2009 November 1
  - The Work Force, 2009 December (Oversized 26)
    - Former Governor George Pataki recorded a video..., 2009 December 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2009 December 1
    - Canastota Schools Groundsworkers Nick Campbell and..., 2009 December 1
    - Otsego County workers demonstrate outside the..., 2009 December 1
    - Capital District Psychiatric Center Local Vice..., 2009 December 1
    - Canastota Schools Bus Driver Suzanne Case, sitting..., 2009 December 1
    - A St. Lawrence County Civil Service Employees..., 2009 December 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 December 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 December 1
    - Canastota Schools Groundsworkers Nick Campbell and..., 2009 December 1
    - Schuyler County Civil Service Employees..., 2009 December 1
    - Gary Farrell, 48, a state Department of..., 2009 December 1
    - Wally Green of the Suffolk County Local in the..., 2009 December 1
    - Liverpool Library workers listen to the..., 2009 December 1
    - South Glens Falls School District Unit President..., 2009 December 1
    - Shenendehowa Central School District Unit Vice..., 2009 December 1
    - An illustration by Graphic Artist Ralph Distin..., 2009 December 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2009 December 1
    - Irving Flaumenbaum speaks at a Civil Service..., 2009 December 1
    - Cover of the December, 2009, Work Force. Workers..., 2009 December 1
  - The Work Force, 2010 January (Oversized 27)
    - More than 80 educational support workers for the..., 2010 January 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Oswego..., 2010 January 1
    - Wendy Nashid-Jackson, a licensed family child care..., 2010 January 1
    - Photo of the Month, January, 2010. Nurse Assistant..., 2010 January 1
    - More than 45 Civil Service Employees Association..., 2010 January 1
    - Town of Southampton Unit members Philip Milo,..., 2010 January 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2010 January 1
    - The Albany Public Library recently celebrated its..., 2010 January 1
    - Wantagh Library Unit members and members from the..., 2010 January 1
    - Long Island Region President Nick LaMorte urges..., 2010 January 1
  - The Work Force, 2010 February (Oversized 27)
    - Mark Brantley, a senior management analyst and..., 2010 February 1
    - Ruby Mims, center, of the Civil Service Employees..., 2010 February 1
    - Illustration by graphic artist Ralph Distin..., 2010 February 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2010 February 1
    - Photo of the Month, February, 2010. Civil Service..., 2010 February 1
    - Certified Nurse Aides Carina Shultis, left, and..., 2010 February 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2010 February 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2010 February 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2010 February 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2010 February 1
    - Photo used as faces of the work force in the 2007..., 2010 February 1
  - The Work Force, 2010 March (Oversized 27)
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2010 March 1
    - SUNY Upstate Local President Kathy Yeldon attended..., 2010 March 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2010 March 1
    - Gloria Smith of the Upstate Medical Center Local..., 2010 March 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2010 March 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2010 March 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2010 March 1
    - New York Governor David Patterson and Civil..., 2010 March 1
    - Team Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2010 March 1
    - New York Assembly Speaker Sheldon Silver listens..., 2010 March 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Central..., 2010 March 1
    - John Glena, husband of Civil Service Employees..., 2010 March 1
    - Kevin Kumor of the Erie County Unit, left, John..., 2010 March 1
    - Quadalupe (Lupe) Johnson, posing at her job at the..., 2010 March 1
    - Brooklyn DDSO Local President Adriane Hudson..., 2010 March 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2010 March 1
    - VOICE/Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2010 March 1
    - Lesly Senatus works the phones at the Rockland..., 2010 March 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2010 March 1
    - State Comptroller Tom DiNapoli addresses Civil..., 2010 March 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2010 March 1
    - VOICE/Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2010 March 1
    - In this illustration for the Civil Service..., 2010 March 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2010 March 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2010 March 1
    - Metropolitan Region office assistant Moses..., 2010 March 1
    - Ruby Mims, the top statewide Civil Service..., 2010 March 1
  - The Work Force, 2010 April (Oversized 27)
    - Village of Cornwall-on-Hudson Unit member Larry..., 2010 April 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Monroe..., 2010 April 1
    - A reprint of a page from the April 17, 1989,..., 2010 April 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2010 April 1
    - Town of Oyster Bay Highway Foreman Electrician..., 2010 April 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2010 April 1
    - Niagara County VOICE/Civil Service Employees..., 2010 April 1
    - Genesee County Nursing Home Certified Nursing..., 2010 April 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) and..., 2010 April 1
    - City of Beacon Unit President Reuben Simmons sees..., 2010 April 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2010 April 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2010 April 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2010 April 1
    - The cover of the Civil Service Employee's..., 2010 April 1
    - Illustration by graphic artist Ralph Distin..., 2010 April 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2010 April 1
    - VOICE/Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2010 April 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2010 April 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2010 April 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2010 April 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) and..., 2010 April 1
    - Michael Patterson, left, hands Civil Service..., 2010 April 1
    - Photo of the Month in the April 2010 Work Force...., 2010 April 1
  - The Work Force, 2010 May (Oversized 27)
    - ?Nearly 100 Civil Service Employees Association..., 2010 May 1
    - ?A Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2010 May 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2010 May 1
    - ?Illustration by graphic artist Ralph Distin in..., 2010 May 1
    - ?Suzanne Case and Robert Hale, Civil Service..., 2010 May 1
    - Rick Martinez, a Civil Service Employees..., 2010 May 1
    - Lizette Marrero of the Long Island Developmental..., 2010 May 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) and..., 2010 May 1
    - ?Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2010 May 1
    - Cattaraugus County Probation Officer and Civil..., 2010 May 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) and..., 2010 May 1
    - Massapequa School District Unit Treasurer Paul..., 2010 May 1
    - ?From left, Pawling School District Unit President..., 2010 May 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2010 May 1
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Geneva..., 2010 May 1
    - Don't Zone Out. The Civil Service Employees..., 2010 May 1
    - The cover of the May 2010 Work Force. More than..., 2010 May 1
  - The Work Force, 2010 June (Oversized 27)